[{"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fd8", "question": "What TV show did \"Young Americans\" spin off from?", "answer": "Dawson's Creek", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdab3320b8cce1e6fda7043", "question": "What common animal is constitutionally protected in Florida?", "answer": "Pigs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60062a6ec9d816e292245c18", "question": "What Jewish German-born American sculptor helped usher in the postminimal art movement in the 1960s?", "answer": "Eva Hesse (She is known for her pioneering work in materials such as latex, fiberglass, and plastics.)", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad54", "question": "What Chilean president was overthrown in 1973 when Augusto Pinochet took power?", "answer": "Salvadore Allende", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c038", "question": "What is the fear of dependence on others known as?", "answer": "Soteriophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d6e92596a59cbdfbd3af", "question": "What was Henry Ford\u2019s original design for a car called?", "answer": "Quadricycle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339055", "question": "Where was Enrico Caruso born?", "answer": "Naples, italy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a03f", "question": "What is Peter's TV network called on the TV show \"Family Guy\"?", "answer": "PTV", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e67", "question": "Who solves crimes in Bayport, located in Barmet Bay?", "answer": "The Hardy Boys", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdc1533469bb8041d07a08a", "question": "What food is also known as \"liberty cabbage\"?", "answer": "Sauerkraut", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c131877e98cb97778975", "question": "Where is Grant\u2019s Tomb?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdc8", "question": "What brand is known as PFK in French-speaking Quebec?", "answer": "KFC", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65797ae7e414034b5aede", "question": "Facebook co-founder Sean Parker was also the co-founder of which company?", "answer": "Napster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff519ebff04d658268c9303", "question": "Which nihilist philosopher famously spoke of \"the death of God?\"", "answer": "Friedrich Nietzsche's philosophy predicted the erosion of organized religions and ethical frameworks.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5971debf89261e916c8e09a3", "question": "The beaver is the national emblem of which country?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff7bfec2b316f4693fb6796", "question": "Where is the goat-racing capital of the world?", "answer": "Tobago", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c690", "question": "What fraction of the Earth's gravity is the moon's?", "answer": "One sixth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58dba546874c93a3298b214f", "question": "What is the name of Princess Anne's second husband", "answer": "Timothy Laurence", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b432", "question": "What year did the Mau Mau Uprising start?", "answer": "1952", "category": "history"}, {"id": "591c3852815febcc896f927e", "question": "What is the second sign of the Zodiac?", "answer": "Taurus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa3d18c73aa70ea0b70af3", "question": "What is the most mountainous country in the world?", "answer": "Bhutan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58be2d038faf425cf37add7a", "question": "In Greek mythology, which of the nine Muses is normally depicted sitting down and holding a lyre?", "answer": "Terpsichore", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5f1648b6f9b80650dbe7f927", "question": "In what movie was the song \"Speechless\"?", "answer": "Aladdin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937eb9a08d98002fdd633b0", "question": "Chopin played what instrument as a child?", "answer": "The piano", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbd9", "question": "In 2003, who became the first Latin\u00adAmerican to hit 500 career home runs in Major League Baseball?", "answer": "Sammy Sosa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be75", "question": "What NBA star was known for his signature spin move, the Dream Shake?", "answer": "Hakeem Olajuwon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c46d", "question": "What color is a huckleberry?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b49e", "question": "Which country hosted the first Olympic Games after World War I?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2a5", "question": "What year was actor Humphrey Bogart born?", "answer": "1899", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad7e928b24f84e0b9f9ffcb", "question": "Seretse Khama was the first President of which country?", "answer": "Botswana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfcb", "question": "What's the ancient Greek word for \"great city\"?", "answer": "Megalopolis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a56", "question": "The Nobel Prize for Literature is presented in what Scandinavian city?", "answer": "Stockholm, Sweden", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ce9", "question": "Tuesday Weld played Thalia Menninger on what TV show?", "answer": "The Many Loves of Dobie Gillis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefa8e36ce05a3942286ed9", "question": "What World War II battle is the setting for the film \"Enemy at the Gates\"?", "answer": "Battle of Stalingrad", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac05", "question": "What is the capital of Nauru?", "answer": "Yaren", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b33", "question": "What 1980s movie soundtrack gave us the #1 hit by the band Berlin titled \"Take My Breath Away\"?", "answer": "Top Gun", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59071d5e3745b36be73039d7", "question": "What operation brought over 1,500 German scientists, engineers and technicians following the end of World War II to the US to aid in military research?", "answer": "Operation Paperclip", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8f5c501dd7bf43be5e82b", "question": "What variety of bananas is the most commonly sold in stores?", "answer": "Cavendish", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4ebd406d333868d34d75f", "question": "To whom was the first .com internet domain registered?", "answer": "Symbolics.com", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339240", "question": "What George Michael song was banned by the BBC and re-edited three times for MTV?", "answer": "I Want Your Sex", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6f4", "question": "How many sides does a trapezoid have?", "answer": "4", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7d7", "question": "What is the handicap of a \"scratch\" golfer?", "answer": "Zero", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ded2caea2747c8aff16d42", "question": "What line on a weather map links all points of equal pressure?", "answer": "Isobar", "category": "science"}, {"id": "592eaec8f83302ff91e4648c", "question": "Mark David Chapman became famous for what in 1980?", "answer": "Shooting John Lennon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339441", "question": "Where does the platoon in the movie \"Full Metal Jacket\" attend boot camp?", "answer": "Parris Island", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bace", "question": "What ingredient must French vanilla ice cream have in it to distinguish it from regular vanilla?", "answer": "Eggs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ac0", "question": "The French phrase \"espirit de corps\" translates in English to what?", "answer": "Comaraderie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc95", "question": "What sport's lingo uses the term \"Peloton\"?", "answer": "Cycling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f719ca9e54d890926f6e2", "question": "In geography, what is a skerry?", "answer": "A small rocky island.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff3cf9e4f032c0db195b491", "question": "In which caste would you most likely find a Hindu priest?", "answer": "Traditionally, priests have come from the Brahmin varna.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecd118ec223966ae8f88bd", "question": "In the 2015 movie, \"Ant-Man\", what hero disappears into a subatomic quantum realm while disabling a Soviet nuclear missile?", "answer": "Wasp", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bb4", "question": "Which famous number was dreaded by people in Orwell\u2019s 1984?", "answer": "101", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2a3", "question": "When was actress Diane Keaton born?", "answer": "1946", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fffa59773838c5c8a417f27", "question": "Ambergris is a waxy substance that originates as a secretion from what animal?", "answer": "Sperm whale", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c643", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Copper?", "answer": "Cu", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d5", "question": "At the end of \"Planet of the Apes\" what monument protruded from the rocks?", "answer": "Statue of Liberty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a189", "question": "In the cartoon \"Wacky Races\", who drove the Buzzwagon?", "answer": "Rufus Ruffcut", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a860", "question": "Belgium's name is derived from what Roman province?", "answer": "Gallia Belgica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f44", "question": "\"Pee-Wee's Big Adventure\" is to recover what beloved stolen item?", "answer": "His bike", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba33c874c93a3298b2139", "question": "Who was the first tennis player to complete the Grand Slam?", "answer": "Don Budge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff20ec831a458464a93c429", "question": "A person who writes the text of an opera, or other long vocal work, is called what?", "answer": "Librettist", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59a553823e1c6f9840ba31a5", "question": "James Alfred Wight was a famous author under which name?", "answer": "James Herriot", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59ae94c7574a5ce6b56b824c", "question": "The cobnut is the fruit of what tree?", "answer": "Hazel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd66246a5bfecdd737e0843", "question": "Who was the oldest Chief Justice appointed to the U.S. Supreme Court?", "answer": "Harlan Stone", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a98a", "question": "What city named its airport after Leonardo da Vinci?", "answer": "Rome", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "593c4a6eb8198b9a2b07795d", "question": "Who played the male lead role in the film \"Clash of the Titans\"?", "answer": "Sam Worthington", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaf4", "question": "Which country borders Kyrgystan to the north?", "answer": "Kazakhstan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be7a", "question": "What company was founded in 1976 by \"the two Steves\"?", "answer": "Apple Computer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be30", "question": "How many players are there in a standard basketball team?", "answer": "Five", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8b9", "question": "What is the main ingredient used to make pesto sauce?", "answer": "Basil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f61", "question": "Eric Arthur Blair was better known by what pen name?", "answer": "George Orwell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fb9", "question": "In Greek mythology, which monster had snakes for hair?", "answer": "Medusa", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4d3", "question": "Canada is divided into provinces and what else?", "answer": "Territories", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c138", "question": "What is a \"kiwano\" a type of?", "answer": "Fruit", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d6f82596a59cbdfbd3b0", "question": "Who invented the lint roller?", "answer": "Nicholas McKay", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f4d", "question": "An episode of what sitcom spawned the phrase \"jumped the shark\"?", "answer": "Happy Days", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae75", "question": "What 20 year old boxer became the youngest WBL heavyweight champ in history, when he beat Trevor Berbick in 1986?", "answer": "Mike Tyson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a61f", "question": "What lake is located several miles west of Carson City?", "answer": "Lake Tahoe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff2121431a458464a93c446", "question": "A person whose age is between 50 and 59, inclusive, is called what?", "answer": "Quinquagenarian", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ff7", "question": "On what TV show did Roger Moore replace James Garner?", "answer": "Maverick", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c162", "question": "The Demologos was the first steam powered what?", "answer": "Warship", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b31a", "question": "Who was the first man to appear on the cover of Playboy Magazine?", "answer": "Peter Sellers", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a36520565ad31a57c7b3", "question": "Who was the last US President born in a log cabin?", "answer": "James A. Garfield", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdffb071cf6db9ac4808cf3", "question": "What U.S. state is home to \"The Raisin Capital of the World\"?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a1", "question": "Who is known as Slim Shady?", "answer": "Marshall Mathers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a422", "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?", "answer": "Wellington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d4700bf8e329de4f87788d", "question": "Who is credited with inventing the saxophone?", "answer": "Adolphe Sax", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b347", "question": "What toy was released in 1958 creating an instant craze among children?", "answer": "The Hula Hoop", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7a6", "question": "What color is the supposedly cursed Hope Diamond?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd662f0a5bfecdd737e084a", "question": "Who was the first woman to become U.S. Secretary of State?", "answer": "Madeline Albright", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601b4ba949076251badbeac6", "question": "The first North American\u00a0English seasonal camp was founded where?", "answer": "St. John's, Newfoundland -- In 1583, Sir\u00a0Humphrey Gilbert, by the\u00a0royal prerogative\u00a0of\u00a0Queen Elizabeth I, founded\u00a0St. John's.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58f169b5f7c52aae91cc07d3", "question": "Who played \"Hawkeye\" in the 1970 film \"MASH\"?", "answer": "Donald Sutherland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe73e5eeec85e375820b274", "question": "Antananarivo is the capital of which large island?", "answer": "Madagascar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c347", "question": "What is the name of the test to determine whether a computer could convincingly imitate a human?", "answer": "The Turing test", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff20f0c31a458464a93c42d", "question": "What is the name of the fishing boat that is featured in the book \"The Perfect Storm\"?", "answer": "The Andrea Gail", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe8f8c601dd7bf43be5e848", "question": "Who said, \"I don't make jokes. I just watch the government and report the facts\"?", "answer": "Will Rogers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e72ceb5d0874f1a5e2d1c28", "question": "What country borders both North Korea and Finland?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339656", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", Marge develops a serious case of what when she gets behind the wheel of her new Canyonero?", "answer": "Road rage", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c8a", "question": "In a nursery rhyme, whose wife \"Could eat no lean\"?", "answer": "Jack Sprat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe3e67938e4e5d4832e6307", "question": "What term did the British press use to describe the air raids carried out by the Germans in 1940 and 1941?", "answer": "The Blitz", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd8a", "question": "Liquid Paper was invented by Bette Graham, the mother of which of the Monkees?", "answer": "Mike Nesmith", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a54", "question": "What university presents the annual Pulitzer Prize journalism awards?", "answer": "Colombia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133988a", "question": "What instrument is Questlove most famous for playing?", "answer": "Drums", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b521", "question": "How loud is a vuvuzela?", "answer": "127 db", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a152", "question": "Whose second album was the chart-topping \"No Need to Argue\"?", "answer": "The Cranberries", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e7d", "question": "During what war was the novel \"War and Peace\" set?", "answer": "Napoleonic Wars", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c53e", "question": "The bone patella is also known as what?", "answer": "The kneecap", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6c6", "question": "Which state is home to Okefenokee National Wildlife Refuge?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338929", "question": "Which Wagner opera shares its name with a doomed ship?", "answer": "The Flying Dutchman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0b3", "question": "In what year did the Chicago Black Hawks win their first Stanley Cup?", "answer": "1934", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d85", "question": "What famous rapper's real name is Christopher Wallace?", "answer": "The Notorious B.I.G.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59067b07ff9c0647b50a805e", "question": "The Gotthard Base Tunnel, which opened on June 1, 2016, is located in which country?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa3f9dc73aa70ea0b70b01", "question": "What does the Japanese term \"Sandai Wagyu\" translate as?", "answer": "Three Big Beefs (Sandai Wagyu are \"the three big beefs\" - Matsusaka, \u014cmi and the most-famous of all, Kobe.)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c736", "question": "What alloy is comprised of copper and zinc?", "answer": "Brass", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59a1a34a12f2a7826b9b8724", "question": "What was E.T.'s favorite candy?", "answer": "Recee's Pieces", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399eb", "question": "How many of the seven dwarfs had mustaches?", "answer": "None", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4e86006d333868d34d747", "question": "Who was the top Australian flying ace in World War I?", "answer": "Robert Little", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ca8", "question": "What kind of fur coat does Cruella De Vil covet?", "answer": "Dalmatian", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae1e", "question": "In which decade was the Three Mile Island nuclear disaster?", "answer": "1970s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a33c", "question": "Lock, Shock and Barrel were characters in which Halloween film?", "answer": "The Nightmare Before Christmas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133996b", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what was the name of Comic Book Guy's dead dog?", "answer": "Chewbacca", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5fa", "question": "The sleeve insignia of a First Class Petty Officer in the US Navy is a spread eagle over how many chevrons?", "answer": "Three", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339549", "question": "What was the name of the dog on the TV show \"The Jetsons\"?", "answer": "Astro", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c061", "question": "What is the nickname of the patient in the game \"Operation\"?", "answer": "Cavity Sam", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ca3dee44f0f6af5b066642", "question": "In which continent would you find Andorra?", "answer": "Europe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe73801eec85e375820b25f", "question": "What islands are located in the Bering Strait between Russia and Alaska?", "answer": "Diomede Islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339176", "question": "Which Seinfeld creator plays himself in the TV show \"Curb Your Enthusiasm\"?", "answer": "Larry David", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7bc", "question": "Of the 88 keys on a piano, how many are black?", "answer": "36", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b150", "question": "In what year did the Berlin Wall come down?", "answer": "1989", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339928", "question": "What was the name of Phoebe\u2019s twin sister on \"Friends\"?", "answer": "Ursula", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58be2ceb8faf425cf37add79", "question": "Lobamba and Mbabane are the legislative and administrative capitals of which African country?", "answer": "Swaziland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133909d", "question": "Who was the Greek god of harvest and agriculture?", "answer": "Demeter", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff2574a31a458464a93c463", "question": "Which restaurant chain fooled the public on 1 April 1998 with the introduction of a fictional sandwich for left-handed people?", "answer": "Burger King released an ad for the fictitious \"Left-Handed Whopper\" on April Fool's Day of 1998.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "590498eecf93664eb104868c", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Oklahoma?", "answer": "Oklahoma City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c192", "question": "Which breed of dog gets its name from the Latin for earth?", "answer": "Terrier", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60121a9563c99d48cd169b04", "question": "What is the common name for enuresis?", "answer": "Bedwetting", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caea", "question": "What invention is Arthur W. Savage often linked with?", "answer": "The radial tire", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b305", "question": "How did Ponce de Leon, Claudius, and Tycho Brahe all die?", "answer": "They were poisoned", "category": "history"}, {"id": "594d06ee1a1c922dd1ac64b2", "question": "Where would you find the Pont Neuf bridge?", "answer": "Paris, France", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abe1", "question": "Tunis is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Tunisia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d077e0870e6f05ba600868", "question": "Who directed the 1995 film \"Boys on the Side\"?", "answer": "Herbert Ross", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adf2", "question": "When did the Hindenburg airship disaster occur?", "answer": "1937", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff66c5852a821ff76ae8b11", "question": "During which year was cocaine removed as an ingredient in Coca Cola?", "answer": "1903", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600f7475a9e54d890926f6f7", "question": "Buchaechum is a traditional Korean what?", "answer": "Fan dance", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a13f", "question": "\"Safety Dance\" was a hit for which band?", "answer": "Men Without Hats", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fb2", "question": "Which German city was the birthplace of the poet Heinrich Heine?", "answer": "Dusseldorf", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5971e01d89261e916c8e09aa", "question": "Who are the actors that play Sam and Dean Winchester in the TV show \"Supernatural\"?", "answer": "Jared Padalecki and Jensen Ackles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba73", "question": "What Latin phrase is used meaning \u201can attorney representing a client for free\u201d?", "answer": "Pro bono", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5902a0f0cad1ec93f27df772", "question": "What do you ferment to make kombucha?", "answer": "Sweetened tea", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa40e0c73aa70ea0b70b0b", "question": "Which U.S. state claims to be the diner capital of the world?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6010c1540775fa611bce67c2", "question": "Dysmorphia is a mental disorder characterized by what?", "answer": "The obsessive idea that some aspect of one's own body part or appearance is severely flawed.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "597cd703e347d002c297e4be", "question": "Which pioneer of modern nursing had a cat called Bismark?", "answer": "Florence Nightingale", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b3589855db0d66a186cb54c", "question": "The Republic of Benin shares a border with which other African country to the east?", "answer": "Nigeria", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf77", "question": "What is the fear of the number 8 known as?", "answer": "Octophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a4e", "question": "What late 1970's hit contains the following line \"Ooh, you make my motor run, my motor run\"?", "answer": "My Sharona", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59008ee5cf842fa4c4ba96b6", "question": "What were \"Jelly Babies\" renamed to in 1918 to mark the end of World War I?", "answer": "Peace Babies", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c326", "question": "The zero of which two temperature scales is known as \"Absolute Zero\"?", "answer": "Kelvin and Rankine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd96bab23c87fd04dd15e1d", "question": "What's the most common first name among the First Ladies of the United States?", "answer": "Elizabeth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4fd", "question": "What do you get when you mix white rum, lime juice, mint and sugar?", "answer": "A Mojito", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397ba", "question": "What U.S. state did the Coneheads settle in after crash landing on earth?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133896e", "question": "Which artist is known as the Father of Impressionism?", "answer": "Camille Pissarro", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff14008b0ee8c595b6d3993", "question": "Artist Andy Warhol suffered from what mental health condition?", "answer": "Hypochondria", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c852877e98cb977789e2", "question": "In which US state can you find George Vanderbilt's extravagant Biltmore Estate?", "answer": "North Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5921fcdca4edfd43a087adc3", "question": "What number is represented by \"V\" in Roman numerals?", "answer": "5", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58b8d5532b42d4a3561a9f01", "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", what is the name of the advertising company Francine interviews for and gets mocked at in the elevator?", "answer": "RBK&S", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338887", "question": "What is the singular of graffiti?", "answer": "Graffito", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7cf01877e98cb97778a49", "question": "Where is the \"Cathedral of Rum\"?", "answer": "Puerto Rico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beab", "question": "Who got his signature left-ear piercing in 1986, after interviewee Liza Minnelli encouraged him to do it?", "answer": "Ed Bradley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af3f", "question": "Eliot Ness is best known for his fight against organized crime in what city?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1dd", "question": "What does the term \"A La Carte\" literally translate to in English?", "answer": "According to the menu", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015e661fe83fe1f2a824bcc", "question": "Which king preceded Queen Victoria?", "answer": "King William IV (who was Victoria\u2019s uncle)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393ed", "question": "What is the name of the funeral home in the TV show \"Six Feet Under\"?", "answer": "Fisher & Sons", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa3cf7c73aa70ea0b70af1", "question": "Where will you find the Beagle Channel?", "answer": "In Tierra del Fuego Archipelago on the southern tip of South America between Chile and Argentina.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d6c", "question": "Who played the role of TV's J. J. Starbuck?", "answer": "Dale Robertson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b888", "question": "Which continents have never hosted the Olympics?", "answer": "Antarctica and Africa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58c8a77a90aac110e4167087", "question": "What mass market tea brand shares a name with an English brewery?", "answer": "Tetley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b86f", "question": "What stickers were spoofs of the Cabbage Patch Kids?", "answer": "Garbage Pail Kids", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff0b62ce662d71a53651003", "question": "\"Philosophiae Naturalis Principia Mathematica\" was written by whom?", "answer": "Isaac Newton", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5cefc199948005ec986edce6", "question": "What powers Iron Man's suit?", "answer": "Arc reactor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c009", "question": "In pool, what color is the eight ball?", "answer": "Black", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8c9", "question": "In the military, what does the abbreviation G.I. stand for?", "answer": "Government Issue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe76861eec85e375820b2a0", "question": "What is the tallest peak in Colorado?", "answer": "Mt. Elbert", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338986", "question": "What name is given to the overweight boy with glasses in the book \"Lord of the Flies\"?", "answer": "Piggy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af8", "question": "What videogame's original series featured the fictional cities Liberty City, Vice City and San Andreas?", "answer": "Grand Theft Auto", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef64f86ce05a3942286e68", "question": "What breed of dog portrayed Toto in 1939's \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "Cairn terrier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd2cff32596a59cbdfbd375", "question": "Who said, \"Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's character, give him power\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fefc22b6ce05a3942286f1a", "question": "The powerful mineral vibranium is mined from which fictional country?", "answer": "Wakanda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7da", "question": "What is the world's largest lake crossed by the equator?", "answer": "Lake Victoria", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5f9f4684af848b908361b876", "question": "As of 2020, what is the highest grossing film of all time without taking inflation into account?", "answer": "Avengers: Endgame", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf83", "question": "In ballet, a lowering of the body by bending the knee is called a what?", "answer": "Fondu", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9f099ff048f679a45aaa0", "question": "Scolionophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "School", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7ccbb877e98cb97778a2a", "question": "Avarua, the capital of the Cook Islands, is located on which South Pacific atoll?", "answer": "Rarotonga", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abce", "question": "What item would you see on the flag of Malta?", "answer": "George Cross", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b31", "question": "What classic movie's title character's first and middle names were Charles Foster?", "answer": "Citizen Kane", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be1b", "question": "What gets changed by the process of transubstantiation?", "answer": "The Catholic Eucharist wafer and wine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c838", "question": "Bauxite ore is mined so it can be processed into what metal?", "answer": "Aluminum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f1b", "question": "What author created the land of Pellucidar?", "answer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cae7", "question": "What is a Supersonic Combustion Ramjet better known as?", "answer": "Scramjet", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba7b", "question": "What team did the Atlanta Braves defeat in the 1995 World Series?", "answer": "Cleveland Indians", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b498", "question": "What year were the Olympic Games hosted in the US for the first time?", "answer": "1904", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c760", "question": "What Greek physician is known as \"The Father of Medicine\"?", "answer": "Hippocrates", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6014c836fbde8045e48466d3", "question": "Where is the observatory where Percival Lowell first theorized the existence of Pluto?", "answer": "Flagstaff, Arizona", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133971b", "question": "What name did Weird Al Yankovic gave to his version of \"Beat It\"?", "answer": "Eat it", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af258f0b63e5727cf5a484a", "question": "Who sang the song \"Boom Boom Boom\"?", "answer": "The Outhere Brothers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6010cb030775fa611bce6801", "question": "What is the name of a word that is spelled the same forwards and backward?", "answer": "Palindrome", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbc6", "question": "What popular soft drink claims to contain 23 flavors?", "answer": "Dr. Pepper", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a00f", "question": "What two metal bands are honored on Beavis and Butt-head's usual t-shirts?", "answer": "AC/DC and Metallica", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c023", "question": "In what city was fashion designer Gianni Versace killed?", "answer": "Miami Beach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae7e", "question": "Franklin D. Roosevelt belonged to which political party?", "answer": "Democratic Party", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a29620565ad31a57c7ae", "question": "Who was the first US presidential candidate to speak at a political convention?", "answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b41", "question": "What was the short lived game show that Betty White won an Emmy award for hosting in 1983?", "answer": "Just Men!", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b76", "question": "What movie director/producer owns Skywalker Ranch, in Marin County, California?", "answer": "George Lucas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef5f4c6ce05a3942286e40", "question": "What was the top grossing movie of 2018?", "answer": "\"Black Panther\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb34", "question": "In the late 1990\u2019s, what candy bar used the ad slogan \"Two for me, none for you\"?", "answer": "Twix", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff0", "question": "Where were fortune cookies invented?", "answer": "United States", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b387", "question": "In which country was the first soccer World Cup held?", "answer": "Uruguay", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fefbdf26ce05a3942286ee5", "question": "In what western television series did Steve McQueen star?", "answer": "Wanted Dead or Alive", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4fa", "question": "What two US state names end with the letter Y?", "answer": "Kentucky and New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff51cc2ff04d658268c931b", "question": "The amphibious landings at Normandy during World War II was codenamed what?", "answer": "Operation Neptune", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff0b1b0e662d71a53650fd2", "question": "Where was the graveyard located where Lord Voldemort made his return?", "answer": "Little Hangleton", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600242bc4be4723ccac2218b", "question": "Which French novelist wrote the seven-volume novel \"In Search of Lost Time\" (often translated as \"Remembrance of Times Past\")?", "answer": "Marcel Proust", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133935f", "question": "What was in the jaws of the swordfish mounted on the wall in the Addams Family house?", "answer": "A human leg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f97", "question": "What TV title role did Jay North play for four seasons?", "answer": "Dennis the Menace", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a76320565ad31a57c7e7", "question": "Why did Michelangelo dislike Raphael?", "answer": "He thought Raphael was copying his work", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339652", "question": "What kind of animal is the title character in the 1954 movie \"Them!\"?", "answer": "Ants", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6e2", "question": "What continent was the original home to the red tomato?", "answer": "South America", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339294", "question": "The movie \"300\" is based on the graphic novel by which comic writer and artist?", "answer": "Frank Miller", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5de", "question": "Who was the model for the official NBA logo?", "answer": "Jerry West", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339643", "question": "What are the names of the male and female archenemies of Rocky and Bullwinkle?", "answer": "Boris and Natasha", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391aa", "question": "Who played James Bond in the 1971 film \"Diamonds Are Forever\"?", "answer": "Sean Connery", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff50fc3d24dd593ee3eacc6", "question": "Which US state has the highest relative humidity?", "answer": "Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a564", "question": "The Delaware River flows into what bay?", "answer": "Delaware Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59f9b770364247bf200fb872", "question": "Which 1993 Disney movie starred Bette Midler as a witch?", "answer": "Hocus Pocus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9dc", "question": "Which fruit can restore your health in Donkey Kong 64?", "answer": "Watermelon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0ee", "question": "Who was the first African-American to be appointed as a US Supreme Court justice?", "answer": "Thurgood Marshall", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a04e", "question": "What is the only superhero film of the 1970s that earned enough at the box office to be a top ten film for that decade?", "answer": "Superman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6010cb0d0775fa611bce6802", "question": "The last leader of the Soviet Union, Mikhail Gorbachev, was in what restaurant commercial?", "answer": "Pizza Hut", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d17", "question": "What newspaper editor wrote the headline \"Spider-Man: Threat or Menace\"?", "answer": "J. Jonah Jameson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397d9", "question": "How many Red Balloons did Nena have in the pop charts in 1984?", "answer": "99", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdabc4e0b8cce1e6fda705d", "question": "Which ingredients are used for making \"ants on a log\"?", "answer": "Raisin, peanut butter and celery", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5b7", "question": "What river was dammed to create the International Amistad Reservoir?", "answer": "Rio Grande River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c466", "question": "Which bodily organ produces urine?", "answer": "The kidneys", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d11", "question": "What movie's first sequel featured the subtitle \"The Other Side\"?", "answer": "Poltergeist", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b730", "question": "What variety of beans is used to prepare Boston baked beans?", "answer": "Navy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a9e95527ccba3ffe45786de", "question": "Malagasy is the native language of which country?", "answer": "Madagascar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c86f", "question": "Enzymes from the papaya fruit are used to make what kitchen staple?", "answer": "Meat tenderizer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cfa", "question": "What was the name of King Arthur's sword?", "answer": "Excalibur", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff3c1bc4f032c0db195b478", "question": "What tribe of Native Americans was the first to encounter the Pilgrims?", "answer": "The Wampanoag", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c163", "question": "What airport has the code MME?", "answer": "Durham Tees Valley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe735d8eec85e375820b253", "question": "Who was the military Chief of Staff of the U.S. Army during World War II?", "answer": "General George Marshall", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6017401844491cbd7c5a17ba", "question": "Who was the only one of Henry VIII\u2019s wives to receive a Queen\u2019s funeral?", "answer": "Jane Seymour", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133945e", "question": "In the movie \"Reservoir Dogs\", who keeps are razor blade in his boot?", "answer": "Mr. Blonde", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b1743a7bb2d29f81593b6f5", "question": "Who wrote the Opera \"The Love for Three Oranges\"?", "answer": "Sergei Prokofiev", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8d8", "question": "What is the maximum number of lines of symmetry a rectangle can have?", "answer": "Four", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ff", "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?", "answer": "Leonardo da Vinci", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59523f68736d4be723796b58", "question": "What year were the Canada's Juno Awards first awarded?", "answer": "1970", "category": "entertainment"}]